(window.webpackJsonp=window.webpackJsonp||[]).push([[0],{13:function(e){e.exports=[{category:"Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",type:"multiple",difficulty:"hard",question:"What%20was%20the%20name%20of%20the%20hero%20in%20the%2080s%20animated%20video%20game%20%27Dragon%27s%20Lair%27%3F",correct_answer:"Dirk%20the%20Daring",incorrect_answers:["Arthur","Sir%20Toby%20Belch","Guy%20of%20Gisbourne"]},{category:"Animals",type:"multiple",difficulty:"easy",question:"What%20is%20the%20scientific%20name%20for%20modern%20day%20humans%3F",correct_answer:"Homo%20Sapiens",incorrect_answers:["Homo%20Ergaster","Homo%20Erectus","Homo%20Neanderthalensis"]},{category:"Entertainment%3A%20Books",type:"multiple",difficulty:"hard",question:"What%20is%20Ron%20Weasley%27s%20middle%20name%3F",correct_answer:"Bilius",incorrect_answers:["Arthur","John","Dominic"]},{category:"Entertainment%3A%20Comics",type:"multiple",difficulty:"easy",question:"Who%20is%20the%20creator%20of%20the%20comic%20series%20%22The%20Walking%20Dead%22%3F",correct_answer:"Robert%20Kirkman",incorrect_answers:["Stan%20Lee","Malcolm%20Wheeler-Nicholson","Robert%20Crumb"]},{category:"Entertainment%3A%20Board%20Games",type:"multiple",difficulty:"medium",question:"At%20the%20start%20of%20a%20standard%20game%20of%20the%20Monopoly%2C%20if%20you%20throw%20a%20double%20six%2C%20which%20square%20would%20you%20land%20on%3F",correct_answer:"Electric%20Company",incorrect_answers:["Water%20Works","Chance","Community%20Chest"]},{category:"Geography",type:"multiple",difficulty:"easy",question:"What%20is%20the%20capital%20of%20Jamaica%3F",correct_answer:"Kingston",incorrect_answers:["Rio%20de%20Janeiro","Dar%20es%20Salaam","Kano"]},{category:"History",type:"multiple",difficulty:"medium",question:"When%20did%20Jamaica%20recieve%20its%20independence%20from%20England%3F%20",correct_answer:"1962",incorrect_answers:["1492","1963","1987"]},{category:"Animals",type:"boolean",difficulty:"easy",question:"Kangaroos%20keep%20food%20in%20their%20pouches%20next%20to%20their%20children.",correct_answer:"False",incorrect_answers:["True"]},{category:"General%20Knowledge",type:"multiple",difficulty:"medium",question:"In%202013%20how%20much%20money%20was%20lost%20by%20Nigerian%20scams%3F",correct_answer:"%2412.7%20Billion",incorrect_answers:["%2495%20Million","%24956%20Million","%242.7%20Billion"]},{category:"History",type:"multiple",difficulty:"medium",question:"How%20old%20was%20Lyndon%20B.%20Johnson%20when%20he%20assumed%20the%20role%20of%20President%20of%20the%20United%20States%3F",correct_answer:"55",incorrect_answers:["50","60","54"]},{category:"Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",type:"multiple",difficulty:"hard",question:"In%20World%20of%20Warcraft%20lore%2C%20who%20organized%20the%20creation%20of%20the%20Paladins%3F",correct_answer:"Alonsus%20Faol",incorrect_answers:["Uther%20the%20Lightbringer","Alexandros%20Mograine","Sargeras%2C%20The%20Daemon%20Lord"]},{category:"Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",type:"boolean",difficulty:"medium",question:"In%20the%20game%20%22Subnautica%22%2C%20a%20%22Cave%20Crawler%22%20will%20attack%20you.",correct_answer:"True",incorrect_answers:["False"]},{category:"Entertainment%3A%20Japanese%20Anime%20%26%20Manga",type:"multiple",difficulty:"medium",question:"What%20is%20the%20name%20of%20the%20device%20that%20allows%20for%20infinite%20energy%20in%20the%20anime%20%22Dimension%20W%22%3F",correct_answer:"Coils",incorrect_answers:["Wires","Collectors","Tesla"]},{category:"Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",type:"multiple",difficulty:"medium",question:"What%20is%20the%20name%20of%20Cream%20the%20Rabbit%27s%20mom%20in%20the%20%22Sonic%20the%20Hedgehog%22%20series%3F",correct_answer:"Vanilla",incorrect_answers:["Peach","Strawberry","Mint"]},{category:"History",type:"multiple",difficulty:"easy",question:"These%20two%20countries%20held%20a%20commonwealth%20from%20the%2016th%20to%2018th%20century.",correct_answer:"Poland%20and%20Lithuania",incorrect_answers:["Hutu%20and%20Rwanda","North%20Korea%20and%20South%20Korea","Bangladesh%20and%20Bhutan"]},{category:"Entertainment%3A%20Television",type:"multiple",difficulty:"hard",question:"Which%20of%20these%20voices%20wasn%27t%20a%20choice%20for%20the%20House%20AI%20in%20%22The%20Simpsons%20Treehouse%20of%20Horror%22%20short%2C%20House%20of%20Whacks%3F",correct_answer:"George%20Clooney",incorrect_answers:["Matthew%20Perry","Dennis%20Miller","Pierce%20Brosnan"]},{category:"Entertainment%3A%20Music",type:"multiple",difficulty:"medium",question:"From%20which%20album%20is%20the%20Gorillaz%20song%2C%20%22On%20Melancholy%20Hill%22%20featured%20in%3F",correct_answer:"Plastic%20Beach",incorrect_answers:["Demon%20Days","Humanz","The%20Fall"]},{category:"General%20Knowledge",type:"boolean",difficulty:"easy",question:"Scotland%20voted%20to%20become%20an%20independent%20country%20during%20the%20referendum%20from%20September%202014.",correct_answer:"False",incorrect_answers:["True"]},{category:"Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",type:"multiple",difficulty:"medium",question:"In%20Left%204%20Dead%2C%20which%20campaign%20has%20the%20protagonists%20going%20through%20a%20subway%20in%20order%20to%20reach%20a%20hospital%20for%20evacuation%3F",correct_answer:"No%20Mercy",incorrect_answers:["Subway%20Sprint","Hospital%20Havoc","Blood%20Harvest"]},{category:"History",type:"multiple",difficulty:"hard",question:"What%20was%20the%20last%20colony%20the%20UK%20ceded%20marking%20the%20end%20of%20the%20British%20Empire%3F",correct_answer:"Hong%20Kong",incorrect_answers:["India","Australia","Ireland"]}]},15:function(e,t,n){e.exports=n(25)},21:function(e,t,n){},24:function(e,t,n){},25:function(e,t,n){"use strict";n.r(t);var r=n(0),a=n.n(r),o=n(9),i=n.n(o),c=(n(21),n(14)),s=n(3),l=n(1),u=n(2);function d(){var e=Object(l.a)(["\n    height: inherit;\n    width: ","%;\n    background-color: #a8a2a8;\n"]);return d=function(){return e},e}function m(){var e=Object(l.a)(["\n    height: 25px;\n    width: 100%;\n"]);return m=function(){return e},e}var h=u.a.div(m()),f=u.a.div(d(),function(e){return e.width}),w=function(e){var t=e.width;return a.a.createElement(h,null,a.a.createElement(f,{width:t||0}))},y=n(6),g=function(e){return decodeURIComponent(e)},p=function(e){for(var t,n,r=e.length;0!==r;)n=Math.floor(Math.random()*r),t=e[r-=1],e[r]=e[n],e[n]=t;return e};function b(){var e=Object(l.a)(["\n  height: 40px;\n  width: 45%;\n  border-radius: 4px;\n  font-size: 13px;\n  font-weight: bold;\n  ","\n"]);return b=function(){return e},e}function E(){var e=Object(l.a)(["\n  font-size: 14px;\n  color: grey;\n  text-align: left;\n"]);return E=function(){return e},e}var v=u.a.span(E()),_=u.a.button(b(),function(e){return e.isCorrect&&"\n    background-color: black;\n    color: #fff\n  "}),A=function(e){var t=e.question,n=void 0===t?{}:t,o=e.handleNextQuestion,i=e.currentQuestion,c=e.saveCurrentAnswer,l=e.totalQuestion,u=Object(r.useState)(p([n.correct_answer].concat(Object(y.a)(n.incorrect_answers)))||[]),d=Object(s.a)(u,2),m=d[0],h=d[1],f=Object(r.useState)({selectedAnswer:null,isAnswered:!1,isAnswerCorrect:!1}),w=Object(s.a)(f,2),b=w[0],E=w[1];Object(r.useEffect)(function(){h(p([n.correct_answer].concat(Object(y.a)(n.incorrect_answers)))||[])},[n]);var A=function(e){var t=e.target.innerText;E({selectedAnswer:t,isAnswered:!0,isAnswerCorrect:t===g(n.correct_answer)})};return a.a.createElement("div",{className:"text-left"},a.a.createElement(v,null,g(n.category)),a.a.createElement("p",null,function(e){switch(e){case"easy":return a.a.createElement("span",null,"\u2605\u2606\u2606");case"medium":return a.a.createElement("span",null,"\u2605\u2605\u2606");case"hard":return a.a.createElement("span",null,"\u2605\u2605\u2605");default:return a.a.createElement("span",null,"\u2606\u2606\u2606")}}(n.difficulty)),a.a.createElement("h5",null,g(n.question)),a.a.createElement("div",{className:"mt-5 d-grid"},a.a.createElement("div",{className:"d-flex justify-content-between mb-4"},m.slice(0,2).map(function(e){return a.a.createElement(_,{onClick:A,disabled:b.isAnswered&&g(e)!==b.selectedAnswer,isCorrect:b.isAnswered&&g(e)===g(n.correct_answer)},g(e))})),a.a.createElement("div",{className:"d-flex justify-content-between"},m.slice(2,4).map(function(e){return a.a.createElement(_,{onClick:A,isCorrect:b.isAnswered&&g(e)===g(n.correct_answer),disabled:b.isAnswered&&g(e)!==b.selectedAnswer},g(e))})),a.a.createElement("div",{className:"mt-5 text-center"},b.isAnswered&&a.a.createElement(a.a.Fragment,null,a.a.createElement("h3",null,b.selectedAnswer===g(n.correct_answer)?"Correct !":"Sorry !"),a.a.createElement("button",{className:"btn btn-outline-secondary mt-2",onClick:function(){c(i,b.isAnswerCorrect),E({selectedAnswer:null,isAnswered:!1,isAnswerCorrect:!1}),o()}},i+1===l?"Finish":"Next Question")))))};function C(){var e=Object(l.a)(["\n  position: absolute;\n  background-color: ",";\n  width: ","%;\n  height: inherit;\n  opacity: .7;\n"]);return C=function(){return e},e}function S(){var e=Object(l.a)(["\n  position: relative;\n  height: 35px;\n  border: 1px solid #dedede;\n  width: 100%;   \n  border-radius: 4px;\n"]);return S=function(){return e},e}function x(){var e=Object(l.a)(["\n  width: 75%;\n  margin: 0 auto;\n"]);return x=function(){return e},e}var j=u.a.div(x()),F=u.a.div(S()),O=u.a.div(C(),function(e){return e.bgColor},function(e){return e.width}),q=function(e){var t=e.currentScore,n=e.maxScore,r=e.lowestScore;return a.a.createElement(j,null,a.a.createElement("div",{className:"d-flex justify-content-between"},a.a.createElement("span",{className:"text-left bold"},"Score: ",t,"%"),a.a.createElement("span",{className:"text-left"},"Max Score: ",n,"%")),a.a.createElement(F,null,a.a.createElement(O,{width:n,bgColor:"lightgray"}),a.a.createElement(O,{width:t,bgColor:"darkgrey"}),a.a.createElement(O,{width:r,bgColor:"black"})))},k=n(13);function N(){var e=Object(l.a)(["\n  position: absolute;\n  bottom: 25px;\n  width: inherit;\n"]);return N=function(){return e},e}function W(){var e=Object(l.a)(["\n  width: 75%;\n  margin: 0 auto;\n"]);return W=function(){return e},e}var H=u.a.div(W()),M=u.a.div(N()),B=function(){var e=Object(r.useState)(k),t=Object(s.a)(e,2),n=t[0],o=t[1],i=Object(r.useState)(!1),l=Object(s.a)(i,2),u=l[0],d=l[1],m=Object(r.useState)(0),h=Object(s.a)(m,2),f=h[0],y=h[1],g=Object(r.useState)({currentScore:0,maxScore:100,lowestScore:0}),p=Object(s.a)(g,2),b=p[0],E=p[1];return Object(r.useEffect)(function(){var e=n.filter(function(e){return e.isAnswerCorrect}).length||0,t=n.length,r=e/f*100,a=(e+(t-f))/t*100,o=e/t*100;E({currentScore:Math.round(r)||0,maxScore:Math.round(a),lowestScore:Math.round(o)})},[n]),a.a.createElement(a.a.Fragment,null,a.a.createElement("div",null,a.a.createElement(w,{width:f/n.length*100})),a.a.createElement(H,{className:"p-4"},u&&a.a.createElement("div",{className:"mt-5"},a.a.createElement("h4",null,"Quiz Finished"),a.a.createElement("p",null,a.a.createElement("h5",null,"Your score: ",b.currentScore," %")),a.a.createElement("button",{onClick:function(){return window.location.reload()},className:"btn btn-outline-secondary"},"Restart Quiz")),!u&&a.a.createElement(a.a.Fragment,null,a.a.createElement("h4",{className:"text-left"},"Question ".concat(f+1," of ").concat(n.length)),n.length>0&&a.a.createElement(A,{handleNextQuestion:function(){f===n.length-1&&d(!0),y(f+1)},question:n[f],currentQuestion:f,saveCurrentAnswer:function(e,t){var r=n.slice();r[e]=Object(c.a)({},r[e],{isAnswerCorrect:t}),o(r)},totalQuestion:n.length}))),a.a.createElement(M,null,a.a.createElement(q,{currentScore:b.currentScore,maxScore:b.maxScore,lowestScore:b.lowestScore})))};n(24);var G=function(){return a.a.createElement("div",{className:"App"},a.a.createElement("div",{className:"container w-50 vh-100 border border-secondary p-0"},a.a.createElement(B,null)))};Boolean("localhost"===window.location.hostname||"[::1]"===window.location.hostname||window.location.hostname.match(/^127(?:\.(?:25[0-5]|2[0-4][0-9]|[01]?[0-9][0-9]?)){3}$/));i.a.render(a.a.createElement(G,null),document.getElementById("root")),"serviceWorker"in navigator&&navigator.serviceWorker.ready.then(function(e){e.unregister()})}},[[15,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.4b1cd836.chunk.js.map